#### Contact

leobina1@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/rubinaatakhanian-msn-rn-cnor-90a39640 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

**CNOR** 

Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS)

Basic Life Support (BLS)

# Rubina Atakhanian, MSN, RN, CNOR

Nurse Leader, Surgical Services

Greater Los Angeles Area

### Summary

An avid advocate of nursing excellence, transformational leadership and staff empowerment with 30 years of operating-room experience, complemented by a diverse background. Recognized as an exceptional team leader with expertise in administrative and quality management, productivity and revenue enhancement, and building positive multi-disciplinary relationships. Experienced in Magnet, nonunionized and union environments, standalone and multistate health systems.

#### Experience

Northridge Hospital Medical Center Manager, Surgical Services Department October 2018 - May 2020 (1 year 8 months) Northridge, California

Huntington Memorial Hospital 15 years

Manager, Surgical Services Department July 2017 - October 2018 (1 year 4 months) Pasadena, California

Registered Nurse/ CST November 2003 - July 2017 (13 years 9 months)

Huntington Hospital, Pasadena Interim Manager, Surgical Servies Department February 2017 - July 2017 (6 months)

Huntington Hospital, Pasadena Supervisor, Surgical Services Department February 2016 - February 2017 (1 year 1 month)

## Education

Western Governors University

Master of Business Administration - MBA, Healthcare

Administration · (2019 - 2020)

Western Governors University

Masters Degree in Nursing Management and Leadership · (2014 - 2016)

Western Governors University

Bachelor of Science - BS, Nursing · (2011 - 2012)